{"result":
[
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"\"You know Nothing,Jon Snow\" was said by?","option1":"Gilly","option2":"Tyrion","option3":"SamTarly","answer":"Ygritte","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Who killed Lord Bolton","option1":"Jon Snow","option2":"Arya Stark","option3":"Rob Stark","answer":"Ramsey Bolton","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Rick's Catchphrase was ","option1":"Wubba bubba LubLub","option2":"Get schwifty","option3":"Tiny Rick","answer":"Wubba Lubba DubDub","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Daenery's largest dragon is ","option1":"Viserion","option2":"Rhaegal","option3":"Rob Stark","answer":"Drogon","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The younger clone Rick transfers his consciousness into was called","option1":"Small Rick","option2":"Teenage Rick","option3":"Young Rick","answer":"Tiny Rick","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The main Rick of foucus is from dimension","option1":"c-173","option2":"b-173","option3":"b-137","answer":"c-137","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"What name was Rick called when he became a Pickle?","option1":"Cholonya","option2":"Stolonye","option3":"Jeff","answer":"Solenya","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The Inter-dimensional Organizations of Ricks is known as","option1":"The League Of Ricks","option2":"Federation Of Ricks","option3":"Coalition Of Ricks","answer":"Council Of Ricks","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The only happy member of the family when Galactic Federation joined Earth was","option1":"Beth","option2":"Summer","option3":"Morty","answer":"Jeff","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The world Rick created when Betty was young was called ___ Land","option1":"Fruppy","option2":"Summer","option3":"Sloppy","answer":"Froopy","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Beth specializes in ___ Surgery","option1":"Cow ","option2":"Pig","option3":"Deer","answer":"Horse","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The name of Rick's formal band with Squanchy and Birdperson was called ___ Curtains","option1":"Bone ","option2":"Skin","option3":"Blood","answer":"Flesh","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Hermiones middle name is","option1":"Shawn","option2":"Queen","option3":"Mieve","answer":"Jean","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The amusement park Rick created in the homeless man was called","option1":"Microscopic park","option2":"Amusing park","option3":"Human park","answer":"Anatomy park","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The only Rick out of the entire council to like Jerry was ","option1":"SealTeam RICK","option2":"President RICK","option3":"Zoomus RICK","answer":"Doofus RICK","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The ruler of the Citadel Of Ricks as at the end of season 3 is ","option1":"Lizard Morty","option2":"Campaign Manager Morty","option3":"Terror Morty","answer":"Evil Morty","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The being created by Rick using Adolf Hitler's and Abraham Lincoln was named","option1":"Adolbraham Hilton","option2":"Adolf Lincoln","option3":"Abraham Hitler","answer":"Abradolf Lincer","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Rick's ex-girlfriend who is a hive-mind is called","option1":"Arthricia","option2":"SuperNova","option3":"Optima","answer":"Unity","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Mr poopyButthole appeared how many times throughout the series so far?","option1":"4","option2":"2","option3":"5","answer":"3","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"During Earths occupation by the Galactic federation,the only member of the family with the urge to rescue Rick was","option1":"Beth","option2":"Morty","option3":"Jerry","answer":"Summer","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"How many Earth like planets did the Smith come across while on the run from the Galactic Federation","option1":"One","option2":"Five","option3":"Two","answer":"Three","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"How did Rick,Morty & Summer cover up the fact that they threw a party and wrecked the house","option1":"Squanchy helped out","option2":"They tapped Beth and Jerry out","option3":"They used an invisible house Shielding Rick created","answer":"They Froze time","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Why did Rick become young to attend Morty and Summer's school","option1":"He fell in love","option2":"To test a new formulaÂ  ","option3":"To help Rick in mathematics","answer":"To kill a vampire","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Rick only got himself arrested by the Galactic Federation to","option1":"To get Schaum Sauce","option2":"To get the federations secret","option3":"To take over the citadel of Ricks","answer":"To replace Jerry as man of the House","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Which character appeared to be real when aliens attacked the family","option1":"Cousin Rick","option2":"Elvinsponster","option3":"Schwifty","answer":"Mr Poopy Butthole","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The name of the train station where trains are boarded to Hogwarts is?","option1":"Kingsquare","option2":"Queencross","option3":"Queensquare","answer":"Kingcross","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The person who killed Harry's Parent was","option1":"Hogrid","option2":"Minerva","option3":"Snape","answer":"Voldemort","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Harry Potter belonged to what house?","option1":"Ravenclaw","option2":"Hufflepuff","option3":"Grandmasters","answer":"Gryffindor","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The sports game highly recognized throughout the series was","option1":"Soccer","option2":"Dragonball","option3":"Squash","answer":"Quidditch","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Harry's parents were killed using ","option1":"A sorcerer's sword ","option2":"Gimly's Knife","option3":"A Dragon Ball","answer":"Adeath curse","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"How were the parasites that infested their household defeated","option1":"They made only bad memories","option2":"They were allergic to sunlight","option3":"They were lactose Intolerant","answer":"They made only good memories","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who was revealed to be the half blood prince?","option1":"Malfoy","option2":"Harry","option3":"Young voldemort","answer":"Snape","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Harry was known popularly as","option1":"The Voldemort Killer","option2":"The Great Wizard","option3":"Half blood prince","answer":"The boy who lived","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Which has muggle blood?","option1":"Neville","option2":"Draco","option3":"Ron","answer":"Hermione","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who was the head of Slytherin when Harry first arrived at Hogwarts?","option1":"Dumbledore","option2":"Flitvrick","option3":"Guirell","answer":"Snape","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Wizarding students get their magical supplies from","option1":"Silicon valley","option2":"Duarisa walls","option3":"Quidditch Ground","answer":"Dragon Alley","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Which house one the house cup in the first series","option1":"Slytherin","option2":"Ravenclaw","option3":"Hufflepuff","answer":"Gryffindor","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Professor Dumbledore dies in which series","option1":"Harry Potter and the Deathly hallows","option2":"Harry potter and the Prisoner of Askaban","option3":"Harry potter and the Order of the Phoenix","answer":"Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Lord Voldemorts group of wizards are known as","option1":"Dark wizards","option2":"Deathly Hallows","option3":"The inferi","answer":"Death eaters","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Lord Voldemorts name is revealed to be","option1":"Geralt Grindewald","option2":"Horace Slughorn","option3":"Thomas Middledith","answer":"Tom Riddle","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The name of the Maximum Security wizards prison is","option1":"Alcatraz","option2":"GuantamoBay","option3":"The Burrow","answer":"Azkaban","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The creatures that guard Azkaban are called","option1":"Devastators","option2":"Besilik","option3":"Destructors","answer":"Dementors","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The main use of Morty to most Ricks is","option1":"Company","option2":"Protection","option3":"Decoys","answer":"Cloakingdevice","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Morty's son ended up becoming a\/an","option1":"Actor","option2":"Reporter","option3":"Analyst","answer":"Novelist","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The name of the top scientist in the world powering Ricks Car battery is","option1":"YeepZanFlorp","option2":"PeezHanyorp","option3":"Neepzanyorp","answer":"ZeepXanflorp","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The name of the prisoner that pickle Rick encountered in the foreign govt agency was?","option1":"Tiger","option2":"Yaguar","option3":"Cougar","answer":"Jaguar","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Before he got fired Jerry Worked at","option1":"A store","option2":"A bank","option3":"A law Firm","answer":"An advertising agency","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"Morty's High School principal was named ___ Vagina","option1":"John","option2":"James","option3":"Patrick","answer":"Gene","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The name of summer boyfriend at the start of the series was","option1":"Nathan","option2":"Kane","option3":"Stark","answer":"Ethan","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The smiths family dog was named","option1":"Flufy","option2":"Fluffles","option3":"Ruffles","answer":"Snuffles","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The task that Jerry gave the meesach that seemed impossible for them was","option1":"Take three strokes off his golf game","option2":"Help him find a job","option3":"Make Betty love him more","answer":"Take two strokes off his golf game","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The name of the character that tries to rape Morty at he tavern was ","option1":"Officer Schoochies","option2":"Mr Mirerva","option3":"King Jellybottle","answer":"Mr JellyBean","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"The co-founder of the Anatomy ParkÂ  was named ","option1":"Dr Krombopalus Michael","option2":"Dr Tophat James","option3":"Dr Philip Jacobs","answer":"Dr Xenon Bloom","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Theron GreyJoy was renamedÂ  ___ in the caprtivity of Ramsey Bolten","option1":"Stench ","option2":"Meek","option3":"Garet","answer":"Reek","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Bran Stark has become one the following","option1":"Two eyed Robin","option2":"One eyed Eagle","option3":"Four eyed Hawk","answer":"Three eyed Raven","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"What is the name of Jon Snows father","option1":"Aeron","option2":"Aegon","option3":"Viserys","answer":"Rhaegar","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Prince Oberyn came to kings landing to kill who","option1":"The hound","option2":"The many faced god","option3":"Cersei","answer":"The vountain","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"\"The man who passes the sentence must swing the sword\" was said by","option1":"Little finger","option2":"Jamie Lannister","option3":"Hudor","answer":"Ned stark","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Who helped Arya to escape Kings landing","option1":"Erenn","option2":"Rob","option3":"Othell","answer":"Yoren","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Who carried out Ned Stark's execution","option1":"Sir Nelcome","option2":"James Slynt","option3":"Rodrick Cass","answer":"Ilyuapyne","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The name of the giant that was killed during the battle against King Bolton was ","option1":"Pongo","option2":"Weg Dar","option3":"Si Valus","answer":"Uhunlum","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Ned Starks sister was named","option1":"Meera","option2":"Myranda","option3":"Myeria","answer":"Lyanna","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The name of Argas Dire Woff was","option1":"ShaggyDog","option2":"Lady","option3":"Meera","answer":"Nyaeria","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The name of the secret group formed by Harry,Ron And Hermione to train students in defensive spells was calledÂ  ","option1":"Hogwarts union","option2":"The Gryffindor's hope","option3":"Hope of Gryffindor","answer":"Dumbledores Army","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The name of King Robert Baratheon's bastard who was found working under a blacksmith and escaped Kings landing alongside Arya was","option1":"Lommy","option2":"Renly","option3":"Lancel","answer":"Gendry","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"After King Roberts death,Tywin Lannister betrothed Cersei to","option1":"Aliser Thorne","option2":"Yohn Royce","option3":"Beric Dondarrion","answer":"Loras Tyrell","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Who was the mastermind in Jofferys death","option1":"Ellaria Sand","option2":"Tyrion","option3":"Petyr Baelish","answer":"Lady Olenna Tyrel","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Who was revealed to be the father of Cerseis Children","option1":"Petyr Baelish","option2":"Qyburn","option3":"Stanis Baratheon","answer":"Jamie Lannister","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The name of the squire allocated to Tyrion Lannister was","option1":"Yohn Royce","option2":"Alliser","option3":"Gendry","answer":"Podrick Payne","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Who tended to Jamie's wound when his hand was cutoff","option1":"The Waif","option2":"Brieme Of Trath","option3":"Grandmaster Pycelle","answer":"Qyburn","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"SyrioForel,Arya's sword master was from","option1":"Essos","option2":"Dorne","option3":"Meeren","answer":"Braavos","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The god which the lady Melisandre worships is called ","option1":"the red god","option2":"the seven","option3":"the many faced god","answer":"the lord of the light","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"jddl","option1":"dkdl","option2":"dlld","option3":"dld","answer":"sod","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"In the beginning of Harry Potter and the chamber of secrets,Ron rescued Harry with the help of ","option1":"His sister","option2":"His parents","option3":"His girlfriend","answer":"His brothers","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"In Harry Potter and the order of Phoenix,Dumbledore's army meetings were heldÂ  in","option1":"his office","option2":"the forbidden forest","option3":"the shrieking shack","answer":"the room of requirement","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Fred & George Weasley are known throughout Hogwarts as","option1":"Genius's","option2":"Trauts","option3":"Bullies","answer":"Pranksters","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who tried to help and prevent him from returning to Hogwarts in Harry Potter and the chamber of secrets","option1":"Donny","option2":"Floppy","option3":"Robby","answer":"Dobby","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Dobby was killed by","option1":"The basilik","option2":"Lucius Malfoy","option3":"Grey black","answer":"Bellatrix Lesrarge","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The name of Hagrids pet spider is ","option1":"Argus","option2":"Grawp","option3":"Fang","answer":"Aragag","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"In Harry Potter and the chamber of secrets,who was the 'defense against the dark arts' teacher","option1":"Fredrick Digory","option2":"Professor Lupin","option3":"Alestor \"Madege\" Moody","answer":"Gildroy Lockhart","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who was responsible for planting Tom Riddle's diary in Ginny's cauldron","option1":"Draco","option2":"Gildroy","option3":"Snape","answer":"Lucius","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Harry defeated the Basilik with ","option1":"The elar wand","option2":"The fang of the beast","option3":"Tom Riddle's Diary","answer":"Sword Of Gryffindor","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Dobby was a house elf for which family","option1":"The Potters","option2":"The Weasleys","option3":"The Gildroys","answer":"The Malfoys","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who's the father of Draco Malfoy","option1":"Scabior","option2":"Thorfinn","option3":"Regulus Black","answer":"Lucius","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What was the name of Harry Potter's Owl?","option1":"Hedwig","option2":"Errol","option3":"Peeves","answer":"Scabbers","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Professor ___ Dumbledore","option1":"James","option2":"Lupin","option3":"Scarry","answer":"Albus","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"People that lack Magical Abilities are called?","option1":"Horcruxes","option2":"Half-blood","option3":"Mortals","answer":"Muggles","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What is the name of Harry's mother","option1":"Hermione","option2":"Jenny","option3":"Molly","answer":"Lily","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who was the prisoner of Azkaban?","option1":"Remus Lupin","option2":"Voldemort","option3":"Draco Malfoy","answer":"Sirius Black","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What is the name of Lord Voldermort's pet","option1":"Firenze","option2":"Kreacher","option3":"Hedwig","answer":"Nagini","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who was the half-giant that was initially the gamekeeper,Keeper of Keys and Grounds of Hogwarts","option1":"Gallert Grindewald","option2":"Viktor Krum","option3":"Frank Bryce","answer":"Rubeus Hagrid","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What is the first name of Harry Potter's only Nephew,a spoiled bully","option1":"Wilbur","option2":"Hubert","option3":"Gunther","answer":"Dudley","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"In Harry Potter movies,what is the name of the widely read daily newspaper","option1":"The Magic Observer","option2":"The Morning Oracle","option3":"The Daily Review ","answer":"The Wizard Times","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Hogwarts official name is","option1":"Hogwarts School of Sorcery & Enchantment","option2":"Hogwarts School of White Magic & Charm","option3":"Hogwarts School of Spells & Incantations","answer":"Hogwarts School of Witchcraft & Wizardry","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What magical object sorts them into houses","option1":"Sorting broom","option2":"Sorting Candle","option3":"Sorting Book","answer":"Sorting Hat","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What is the surname of Harry Potter's aunt and Uncle that raised him","option1":"Thornbury","option2":"Berkeley","option3":"Quedgeley","answer":"Dursley","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Which of these was a close friend of Harry's parents but betrayed them","option1":"igor Karkaroff","option2":"Sirius Black","option3":"Fenrir Greyback","answer":"Peter Pettigrew","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What is the name of the Only British Village(northwest of Hogwarts) inhabited solely by wizards,witches and other magical being","option1":"Hogshead","option2":"Hogsweed","option3":"Hogsback","answer":"Hogsmeade","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The giant dog that guards the Philosopher's stone has how many heads","option1":"4","option2":"2","option3":"5","answer":"3","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Harry meets Ron and Hermione where for the first time","option1":"On a ship","option2":"In an elevator","option3":"In a windmill","answer":"on a train","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"Who became Harry's biggest rival at Hogwarts","option1":"Frank bryce","option2":"Viktor Krum","option3":"Cedric Diggory","answer":"Draco Malfoy","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What position does Harry have in his Hogwarts team at the game of Quidditch?","option1":"Beater","option2":"Chaser","option3":"Keeper","answer":"Seeker","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"What kind of creature is a Basilik","option1":"Spider","option2":"Scorpion","option3":"Three-headed-Monster","answer":"Serpent","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The scar on Harry's head resembles which of these ","option1":"Hashtag","option2":"Letter V","option3":"Star","answer":"Lightning-bolt","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Harry_Potter","question":"The Azkaban Fortress\/prison has what kind of shape when seen from top","option1":"Pyramid","option2":"Pentagon","option3":"Rhombus","answer":"Triangle","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The house baratheon are well known throughout the westeros for their ___ hair","option1":"Brown","option2":"Silver","option3":"Gold","answer":"Black","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"Hodons real name was revealed to be","option1":"Sandor","option2":"Kindu","option3":"Philis","answer":"Wylis","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The first person Daenerys ordered her dragons to kill was","option1":"The slave masterat veeren","option2":"Daxos","option3":"Doreah","answer":"Pree","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Game_Of_Thrones","question":"The sigil of House stark is","option1":"Bear","option2":"Lion","option3":"Fox","answer":"Wolf","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Naruto ___","option1":"Obito","option2":"Sharingan","option3":"Uzakaki","answer":"Uzumaki","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who was Narutos teacher?","option1":"Sakura","option2":"Minato","option3":"Obito","answer":"Iruka","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"The village Naruo lived is called?","option1":"Kyuubigakure","option2":"Sunagakure","option3":"Uzumagakure","answer":"Konohagakure","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which of these is not a member of the Nora clan?","option1":"Shikaku","option2":"Ensui","option3":"Yoshino","answer":"Jiraiya","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which of these people has been Hokage the most?","option1":"Tsunade","option2":"Kakashi Hatake","option3":"Hashirama senju","answer":"Hiruzen Sarutobi","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who has not been considered for Hokage?","option1":"Shikamaru","option2":"Danzo","option3":"Jiraiya","answer":"Sakura","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which famed clan was completely massacred?","option1":"Hyuuga","option2":"Uzumaki","option3":"Nara","answer":"Uchicha","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which one of these is not one of Naruto's specialist?","option1":"Shadow clone jutsu","option2":"Sexy no justsu","option3":"Rasengun","answer":"Chidori","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"How did Hidan die?","option1":"He was starved","option2":"His god betrayed him?","option3":"HeÂ  was trapped in Shadow possession Jutsu","answer":"He can't die","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What is Tsunade's drug?","option1":"Men","option2":"Alcohol","option3":"Work","answer":"Gambling","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which friend died during the Fourth Great War?","option1":"Hinata","option2":"Choji","option3":"Shikamaru","answer":"Neji","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which ninja cannot do ninjutsu? ","option1":"Tenten","option2":"Might guy","option3":"Kakashi","answer":"Rock Lee","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who does Naruto marry eventually?","option1":"Sakura","option2":"Temari","option3":"Tenten","answer":"Hinata","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What is team Asuma's favorite food?","option1":"Ramen","option2":"Taiyaki","option3":"Sushi","answer":"BBQ","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which trait is common inthe Uzumaki clan?","option1":"The ability to use Rasengan","option2":"Blue eyes","option3":"Spunk","answer":"Red hair","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which of these unlikely people is a fan of Jiraiya's books?","option1":"Tsunade","option2":"Konohamaru","option3":"Orochimaru","answer":"Kakashi","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who gave their life to Gaara?","option1":"Kankuro","option2":"Sasori","option3":"Fugi","answer":"Chiyo","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who is the first enemy Naruto faces?","option1":"Zabuza","option2":"Kabuto","option3":"Orochimaru","answer":"Mizuki","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"How does Karin heal you?","option1":"You summon her","option2":"You punch her","option3":"You think of her","answer":"You bite her","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who wasthe youngest jonin?","option1":"Sakura","option2":"Itachi","option3":"Neji","answer":"Kakashi","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What piece of jewelry do the Akatsuki wear? ","option1":"Chains","option2":"Bracelets","option3":"Noserings","answer":"Rings","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"The Ring worn by Orochimaru(as an akatsuki member means)","option1":"Scarlet","option2":"Boar","option3":"South","answer":"Sky","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What does Tsunade summon?","option1":"Lizard","option2":"Frog","option3":"Toad","answer":"Slug","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What was Sasuke's goal at the beginning of Naruto?","option1":"Take over the world","option2":"Become Hokage","option3":"Impress Sakura","answer":"Kill his brother","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which sword did Suigetsu originally wield?","option1":"Samehada","option2":"Nuibari","option3":"Shibuki","answer":"Kubikiribocho","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What does ANBU mean?","option1":"Special unit forces and Recruits","option2":"Hidden Agendas of Shinobi and Allied Tactics","option3":"Undercover Ninjas:Black operations","answer":"Special Assassination and Tactical Squad","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What does Gaara's tattoo mean?","option1":"Orphan","option2":"Hate","option3":"Monster","answer":"Love","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who created the Akatsuki","option1":"Orochimaru","option2":"Tobi","option3":"Itachi","answer":"Yahiko","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What is Sasuke's team called?","option1":"Tiki","option2":"Toka","option3":"Toku","answer":"Taka","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who performs the Evening Elephant technique?","option1":"Ino","option2":"Kakashi","option3":"Neji","answer":"Guy","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Which of these characters has Kurama's chakra?","option1":"Menma","option2":"Guren","option3":"Haku","answer":"Sora","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"There's an episode called 'Laughing __'?","option1":"Orochimaru","option2":"Kakashi","option3":"Shikamaru","answer":"Shino","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"What was the name of Madara's jutsu?","option1":"End of Suffering","option2":"Endless Red Moon","option3":"Reflections in Red","answer":"Eye of the moon","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Naruto","question":"Who is the last person Naruto battled in Shippuden?","option1":"Kurama","option2":"Kaguya","option3":"Madara","answer":"Sasuke","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Who makes the statement \"How you doing\"?","option1":"Phoebe","option2":"Chandler","option3":"Ross","answer":"Joey","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"How many seasons did Friends have in total?","option1":"8","option2":"7","option3":"9","answer":"10","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What is Rachel Green's real name?","option1":"Lisa LeBlanc","option2":"Lisa Kudrow","option3":"Courtney Cox","answer":"Jennifer Aniston","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What two Friend's combination ever got married in real life?","option1":"Ross and Rachel","option2":"Joey and Phoebe","option3":"Chandler and Monica","answer":"Ross and Monica","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"The first season of Friends was in what year?","option1":"1998","option2":"1996","option3":"1995","answer":"1994","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What two combinations never kissed in Friends?","option1":"Ross and Phoebe","option2":"Chandler and Rachel","option3":"Ross and Monica","answer":"Joey and Monica","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Who runs a coffee shop and also likes Rachel?","option1":"Janice","option2":"Sarah","option3":"Joey","answer":"Gunther","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What award was Joey nominated for in the Soapie Award in season 7 episode 18?","option1":"Best Dressed Actor","option2":"Funniest Character","option3":"Best replacement","answer":"Favorite Returning","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What is the name of the student Ross dated?","option1":"Janice","option2":"Emily","option3":"Emma","answer":"Elizabeth","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What is the name of Ross's son?","option1":"Josh","option2":"Emily","option3":"Jade","answer":"Ben","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Rachel's middle name is ?","option1":"Marie","option2":"Hut","option3":"Michelle","answer":"Karen","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What is Joey and Chandler's favorite tv show?","option1":"ER","option2":"Friends","option3":"Seinfeld","answer":"Baywatch","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Joey's favorite food?","option1":"Pizza","option2":"Chicken","option3":"Tacos","answer":"Sandwiches","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Who was the best man at Chandler and Monica's wedding?","option1":"His dad","option2":"Gunther","option3":"Joey","answer":"Ross","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What is the name of Phoebe's twin sister?","option1":"Monica","option2":"Janice","option3":"Phoenix","answer":"Ursurla","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Chandler married?","option1":"Rachel","option2":"Janice","option3":"Emily","answer":"Monica","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Which workmate younger than Rachel did she date?","option1":"Colin","option2":"James","option3":"Kelly","answer":"Tag","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Matt Leblanc is the real name for who?","option1":"Ross","option2":"Chandler","option3":"Gunther","answer":"Joey","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Name of the millionaire Monica dated that wanted to conquer the Ultimate Fighting Championship?","option1":"Ben Tucks","option2":"Tag Gunner","option3":"Pete Gunner","answer":"Pete Becker","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Name of Rachel Greens sister that dated Ross?","option1":"Emily","option2":"Sandra","option3":"Amy","answer":"Jill","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"How many sisters did Rachel have?","option1":"1","option2":"3","option3":"0","answer":"2","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Name of the girl Ross dated that Rachel convinced to go bald?","option1":"Emily","option2":"Amy","option3":"Phoebe","answer":"Bonnie","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Ross' wife left him because ...","option1":"He was broke","option2":"She didn't love him","option3":"He is self-confident","answer":"She is a lesbian","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Name of Ross. ex-wife(Susan)'s new girlfriend?","option1":"Jane","option2":"Kenny","option3":"Cam","answer":"Susan","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Phoebe eventually got married to?","option1":"Mark","option2":"Joey","option3":"Chandler","answer":"Mike","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Which of the characters did we meet first in the series?","option1":"Rio","option2":"Denver","option3":"Berlin","answer":"Tokyo","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Real name of El Professor in the series?","option1":"Alvaro","option2":"Javier","option3":"Miguel","answer":"Sergio","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"What bank was robbed in the first part of the series?","option1":"Royal ground of Spain","option2":"Al pero lo Mueto","option3":"Le casa de papel","answer":"Royal mint of Spain","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Professor got married to?","option1":"Nairobi","option2":"Tokyo","option3":"Rio","answer":"Raquel","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"The whole point from the third season is to?","option1":"Make more money","option2":"Teach tokyo a lesson","option3":"Save Denver","answer":"Save Rio","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Bella ciao actually means?","option1":"onto the next one","option2":"Great bidding","option3":"Goodbye brother","answer":"Goodbye beautiful","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Which of the robbers die first ?","option1":"Nairobi","option2":"Moscow","option3":"Rio","answer":"Oslo","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Who killed Oslo?","option1":"The Police","option2":"Denver","option3":"Professor","answer":"Helsinki","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Money Heist is currently owned by?","option1":"HBO","option2":"Disney","option3":"Aba Boys limited","answer":"Netflix","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"What is the Professors name in real life?","option1":"Alvaro Contel","option2":"Sergio Contel","option3":"Sergio Morte","answer":"Alvaro Morte","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"How many seasons of Money Heist are ther currently","option1":"2","option2":"3","option3":"5","answer":"4","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Who was shot at the ending of season3?","option1":"Denver","option2":"Raquel","option3":"Rio","answer":"Nairobi","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"What popular song is known from the show?","option1":"Te quiero","option2":"Te Odio","option3":"Bella Senorita","answer":"Bella Ciao","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"This series is also called?","option1":"Elite","option2":"Jao Te quierro","option3":"Le quasa de quintero","answer":"Le casa de papel","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Name of the pregnant inspector in Money Heist?","option1":"Tatiana Nimri","option2":"Alex Ruckio","option3":"Tatiana Murillo","answer":"Alicia Sierra","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Who shot Ghost?","option1":"Angela","option2":"Tommy","option3":"Mark","answer":"Tariq","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Ghost's name is","option1":"James Cole","option2":"Tommy Hilfinger","option3":"John Doe","answer":"James St'Patrick","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"How many seasons do power have?","option1":"5","option2":"4","option3":"7","answer":"6","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Name of Ghost's wife?","option1":"Anita","option2":"Keisha","option3":"Angela","answer":"Tasha","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Tommy ......","option1":"Hilfinger","option2":"St'Patrick","option3":"Julio","answer":"Egan","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Name of Ghost daughter that died","option1":"Rihanina","option2":"Tariqa","option3":"Lauren","answer":"Reina","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Why was Keisha killed?","option1":"To wade off the Feds","option2":"To protect Tommy","option3":"She killed Reina","answer":"To protect Tariq","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"The first season of the series was in","option1":"2013","option2":"2016","option3":"2015","answer":"2014","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"The first season of the series was in","option1":"2016","option2":"2015","option3":"2018","answer":"2017","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"The series theme song starts with ","option1":"Bright lights, Bright city","option2":"They are never catching us, no","option3":"Oh nanana","answer":"They say this is a big rich town","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Power theme song is by","option1":"Nas","option2":"2pac","option3":"Rackim","answer":"50 cent","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"First season of Power had how many episodes","option1":"7","option2":"9","option3":"10","answer":"8","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Angela ......","option1":"Valor","option2":"Egan","option3":"Keisha","answer":"Valdes","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Who killed Tommy's father?","option1":"Ghost","option2":"Tariq","option3":"Dre","answer":"Tommy","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Tommy's father is a member of what gang?","option1":"Cuchillos","option2":"Teresi","option3":"Santos","answer":"Sicillian","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Where did Dre die?","option1":"In the club","option2":"In his house","option3":"In Ghost's car","answer":"In the Prison","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Which of these combinations are family?","option1":"Tokyo and Berlin","option2":"Rio and Nairobi","option3":"Oslo and Helsinki","answer":"Denver and Moscow","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Who is the detective Ghost is dating?","option1":"Tasha","option2":"Lakeisha","option3":"Reina","answer":"Angela","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"What is the name of Ghost's club?","option1":"Power","option2":"Elite","option3":"Owned","answer":"Truth","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"What season did Ghost go to Jail?","option1":"3","option2":"2","option3":"5","answer":"4","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"What season did Tommy go to Jail?","option1":"1","option2":"3","option3":"4","answer":"2","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Power","question":"Who killed Rolla in season 1?","option1":"Kanan","option2":"Tommy","option3":"Miguel Alvarez","answer":"Ghost","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"For the first part, who mainly ran the show in the bank?","option1":"Nairobi","option2":"Tokyo","option3":"Moscow","answer":"Berlin","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"How many robbers were there initially excluding Professor?","option1":"5","option2":"6","option3":"7","answer":"8","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Who is known for his\/her sarcasm?","option1":"Rachel","option2":"Gunther","option3":"Ross","answer":"Chandler","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Chandler ......","option1":"Ting","option2":"Ring","option3":"Ming","answer":"Bing","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"Which of these are siblings?","option1":"Ross and Rachel","option2":"Joey and Phoebe","option3":"Joey and Rachel","answer":"Ross and Monica","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Friends","question":"What is Ross' popular word for defending the reason he slept with someone else while dating Rachel?","option1":"I did not mean it","option2":"It was the devil","option3":"I was drunk","answer":"We were on a break","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Who is Denver dating?","option1":"Nairobi","option2":"London","option3":"Tokyo","answer":"Monica","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Who was the most outspoken hostage in the first part?","option1":"Monica","option2":"Kelly","option3":"Satos","answer":"Arturo","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"When Tokyo went back into the building, she went on a\/an","option1":"Helicopter","option2":"Airplane","option3":"Bus","answer":"Motorcycle","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Who is the youngest robber?","option1":"Tokyo","option2":"Berlin","option3":"Denver","answer":"Rio","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Money_Heist","question":"Which of these is not a part of the team that tried to save Rio?","option1":"Raquel","option2":"Monica","option3":"Helsinki","answer":"Moscow","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Who was going to destroy the ring?","option1":"Legolas","option2":"Gandalf","option3":"Porto","answer":"Frodo","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"What evil thing did Gollum do initially for the ring?","option1":"He slayed his mother?","option2":"He slied his village","option3":"He killed his guardian","answer":"He killed his brother","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"How many main parts are there?","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"4","answer":"3","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"The first part of Lord of the rings was called","option1":"Return of the ring","option2":"The Genesis of the ring","option3":"The Destruction of the ring","answer":"The Fellowship of the ring","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"The movie has a rating of what on imdb","option1":"7.","option2":"9.","option3":"6.","answer":"8.","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which of these is not a character in Movie?","option1":"Aragorn","option2":"Gandalf","option3":"Legolas","answer":"Dumbledore","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Who followed Frodo on his journey","option1":"Aragorn","option2":"Gimli","option3":"Pippin ","answer":"Samwise","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Frodo ........ and Samwise ..... respectively","option1":"Gamgee, Baggings","option2":"Smeagol, Gollum","option3":"Collin, Cox","answer":"Baggings, Gamgee","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"What is Gollums name?","option1":"Frenden","option2":"Alusa","option3":"Smeaker","answer":"Smeagol","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"How old is Smeagol?","option1":"520","option2":"673","option3":"952","answer":"589","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"The most powerful wizard?","option1":"Gandalf","option2":"Radagast","option3":"Alatar","answer":"Saruman","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"What were the spirits Aragorn went to beg for help called?","option1":"Azkyul","option2":"Wringaiths","option3":"Nazguls","answer":"Army Of The Dead","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Where did they fight the final battle?","option1":"Moria","option2":"Isengard","option3":"Rohans","answer":"Black gate","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which of these Battles never happened?","option1":"Battle of Minas Trith","option2":"Battle of Helms deep","option3":"Battle at the Black gate","answer":"Nazguls vs URUK Hai","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"What is the name of Boromirs younger brother?","option1":"Aragorn","option2":"Gimli","option3":"Flogskavir","answer":"Faramir","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Frodo is a\/an ......","option1":"Dwarf","option2":"Elf","option3":"Wizard","answer":"Hobbit","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"The eye belongs to","option1":"Saruman","option2":"Sandril","option3":"Sarton","answer":"Sauron","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Who is the dark Lord?","option1":"Morgoth","option2":"Galadriel","option3":"Saruman","answer":"Sauron","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which is the strongest?","option1":"The Dark Lord","option2":"Saruman","option3":"Gandalf","answer":"Morgorth","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"The Black Riders are actually called","option1":"Angmar","option2":"Barlog","option3":"Gimlis","answer":"Nazgul","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"How many Nazguls are there","option1":"7","option2":"6","option3":"8","answer":"9","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Name of the town Frodo Baggings is from?","option1":"Wildock","option2":"Bag Smial","option3":"Shire","answer":"Bag End","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which is not one of the hobbits introduced to us?","option1":"Pippin","option2":"Frodo","option3":"Merry","answer":"Legolas","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which of these is a dwarf?","option1":"Samwise","option2":"Aragorn","option3":"Frodo","answer":"Gimli","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which of these is an elf?","option1":"Aragorn","option2":"Gimli","option3":"Bilbo","answer":"Legolas","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Lord_OF_The_Rings","question":"Which of these is human?","option1":"Nazgul","option2":"Mordorth","option3":"Gandalf","answer":"Aragorn","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"The Flash","question":"Protagonist in series ?","option1":"Vibe","option2":"Kerry Carter","option3":"Bill Smith","answer":"Barry Allen","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"The Flash","question":"Wally west vs Barry","option1":"Usain Bolt","option2":"Draw","option3":"Barry Allen","answer":"Wally wesy","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Who was Darth Varder?","option1":"Lucas","option2":"Sam","option3":"Jake","answer":"Annakin","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Who was Darth Varder's son ","option1":"Annobi","option2":"Leia","option3":"Anakin","answer":"Luke","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Who trained Aankin Sky-walker?","option1":"Qui-Gon","option2":"Master Yoda","option3":"Meetra","answer":"Obi-wan Kenobi","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Obi-wan Kenobi was a ","option1":"Sith","option2":"Varder","option3":"Darth","answer":"Jedi","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"The first movie was called","option1":"The return of the Jedi","option2":"The rise of the Jedi","option3":"The last Jedi","answer":"A new hope","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"The first movie of the star wars came out in what year?","option1":"1974","option2":"1981","option3":"1972","answer":"1977","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Which of these robots in well known in star wars","option1":"x2r2","option2":"a2b2","option3":"c2d2","answer":"r2d2","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Which of these robots is well known in star wars?","option1":"C-Q30","option2":"C-Q10","option3":"C2D2","answer":"C-3PO","level":"hard"},
{"movie":"Star_Wars","question":"Which of these characters cannot be affiliated with this Movie?","option1":"Yoda","option2":"Luke Skywalker","option3":"Obiwan","answer":"Piddrow Skywalker","level":"medium"},
{"movie":"Titanic","question":"Titanic wreck happened on a ","option1":"Boat","option2":"Airplane","option3":"Bus","answer":"Ship","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Titanic","question":"Titanics main lovers were","option1":"Romeo and Juliet","option2":"Jack and Jill","option3":"Bill and Kate","answer":"Jack and Rose","level":"easy"},
{"movie":"Rick_And_Morty","question":"How many seasons does this series currently have?","option1":"2","option2":"1","option3":"3","answer":"4","level":"medium"}
]
}
]}
